And I think taken together, that gives us confidence that the study
is performing.
As expected, in terms of the differences between the active and the control arm.
But not more we can say at this point until we ultimately read out the trial.
I think for us, clearly with Remy Bruteneb, in addition to looking at annualized relapse
rate and MRI performance, how it performs in disability progression will be important
to understand is Remy something that would be used?
In a setting post the B-cell antibodies, or could it be used in a setting in line or ahead of the B-cell antibodies?
And this will all be data driven.
And obviously, once we see that data, we'll be able to provide better guidance on that use.
But that's probably about as much as we can provide at this point.
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Richard Foster from JP Morgan.
Please go ahead.
Hi, thanks for taking my question.
Just another question on Pella Carson.
We've seen some other cardiovascular trials recently suffer from high levels of drop-ins
of existing therapies.
So, wondering how you've controlled for that in the Horizon trial, just thinking about
it in relation to, I suppose, PCSK9s, but also for GLP-1s and SGLT2s, given the 25%
of patients that are diabetics.
So, how should we think about that level of use?
And potentially, the effect of that?
And potentially, the impact on any benefits of Pella Carson?
Thanks very much.
Yeah, thanks, Richard.
I mean, it is important to know we study Pella Carson on top of optimized background lipid
lowering therapy.
I mean, our current estimate is that the number of patients who were on incretin-based
therapies in the study is less than 10%.
I mean, we estimate it to be around 6%.
So, we don't believe that if there was any effect from those medicines.
In the setting, that we wouldn't expect that to impact the results here.
So, when we look at it overall, it's as we, more or less as we planned in terms of background
therapy.
And so, we don't think that will be a major swing factor, at least based on what we can
see so far.
Thank you.
Did you?
Okay.
Yeah, go ahead.
Go ahead, Richard.
No, it was just on PCSK9s.
Just one quick follow-up.
Was that controlled as well?